### **ANTHONY BATTINELLI**

Stamford, CT

Phone: 203-249-1460 | Email: tbj86@outlook.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/anthony-battinelli | Portfolio: https://tbgolfer86.github.io/Portfolio/

GitHub: https://github.com/tbgolfer86

#### SUMMARY

Critical thinking full stack web developer with a web development certificate from the University of Connecticut. Experience in front and back end design utilizing a combination of strong communication, collaboration, problem-solving, analytical, and organizational skills. Ability to pay strong attention to detail in a fast-paced and diverse team environment consistently creating solutions that exceed expectations.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Softwares/Platforms: VSCode, GitHub, Heroku, Slack, Zoom, Schwab Streetsmart Edge

**Software Languages:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, SQL Databases,

Handlebars

### **PROJECTS**

**Recipe Finder** | https://github.com/tbgolfer86/Recipe-Finder **Link to Deployed Project** https://tbgolfer86.github.io/Recipe-Finder/

- Application that fetches food and drink recipes based on ingredients selected by the user
- Responsible for design and development of user interface and Javascript functionality
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bulma Framework, 2 APIs

Scorecards | https://github.com/sampaul10/scorecard-app

Link to Deployed Project https://sam-scorecard-app.herokuapp.com/

- Application that allows a golfer to record hole-by-hole scores and view score history
- Worked as team lead to coordinate and execute tasks and responsibilities in a timely manner
- Responsible for front and back-end Javascript, layout and design, Handlebars views
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bulma Framework, Node.js, Express.js, SQL Database, Handlebars

Recipe Finder | https://github.com/tbgolfer86/Recipe-Finder

Link to Deployed Project https://tbgolfer86.github.io/Recipe-Finder/

- Application that fetches food and drink recipes based on ingredients selected by the user
- Responsible for front end design and execution, Javascript functionality
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bulma Framework, 2 APIs

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Caddie Burning Tree Country Club

2018 - Present

Greenwich, CT

Integrated superior customer service with golf knowledge to deliver a quality and consistent on-course experience in an upscale private country club environment.

Key Accomplishments:

• Advised members and guests of all ages and skill levels with on-course strategy and decision

making to maximize their potential and achieve better results

- Requested by membership and golf staff for off-site competitive tournaments
- 2020 Women's Club Champion Caddie
- 2021 Men's Club Champion Caddie

# Assistant Golf Professional Burning Tree Country Club

2011 - 2017

Greenwich, CT

Utilized strong communication and critical thinking skills to provide superior customer service and junior golf instruction in a private country club environment.

- Key Accomplishments:
  - Collaborated with a team of 8 to provide high quality customer service
  - Coordinated and scheduled tee times for over 200 golfing members
  - Ensured accurate golf lesson scheduling for 4 other golf professionals
  - Provided junior golf instruction in both 1-on-1 settings and groups of up to 20
  - Established and maintained relationships with members by answering their questions and assisting them in a detail oriented manner
  - Managed over \$150,000 in merchandise using the Jonas System Point-of-Sale software
  - Edited monthly club newsletter
  - Finished Top-10 on Metropolitan PGA Assistants Tour
  - Attained TaylorMade and Titleist golf staff player sponsorships
  - Earned eligibility for the PGA of America's Professional Golf Management Program by passing the Playing Ability Test

#### **EDUCATION**

**Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp Certificate:** University of Connecticut, Virtual May 2023 A 24 week intensive program focused on getting technical programming skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, and SQL Databases.

**Bachelor's Degree in Economics:** University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT 2004 – 2009